Hi everyone! Welcome to a new video, fake versus real and today I have a latex
corset or rather two latex corsets. One from HW Design and a ripper from eBay.
So this is my HW Design corset. It is a great basic and well-known in the latex
scene. It's quite heavy, my arm is starting to hurt. And this is the one I found on
eBay because I was on eBay and I saw a picture I was like wait a sec I know
this and realized well this is probably some kind of China ripoff so the hard
facts this was 600 bucks and this was 56 euro plus point for that one was also
that it was delivered really fast so within a few days well this was like
round about 16 weeks until it was delivered but price and delivery time is
not everything so is it the affordable alternative or not let's find out
starting with the original I'm trying to put this on by myself they're like
shoulder straps and I love to combine a latex corset and latex leggings with a
normal t-shirt done a few pictures with this look and I love them I think the
overall idea to combine casual t-shirts with latex is just great
Maybe you see why I said it is a great basic corset.
You should have a basic corset in your closet.
I'd say we have two layers of 1mm, so around about 2mm in total thickness of the overall corset.
Then we have a lot of boning, spiral boning throughout the corset on every side.
A metal basket here in the middle.
I also ordered additional D-rings to maybe attach something if I want to.
And the crotch straps are just for the look.
I really like this look also with the shoulder straps so you may say the price is a bit high but
I mean latex is handmade I have made a corset myself and I know that is a lot of work I really
took me hours and hours and it wasn't as good as this one so I think you need to pay
money if you want to have good latex stuff it is just the way it is nevertheless I'm going to show
you the other one now so you see why you maybe need to pay a bit more money for
good latex stuff. So let's put the fake one on and I can already tell it's way more wobbly.
Let's try this.
And now I'm confused.
I have no idea how I should close this strap now because there are no holes anymore here.
It's way too long and I added suspenders so another strap hanging around here.
Let's see if the other one fits, I doubt it.
Nope.
So it's a no for the crotch straps. Let's try the shoulders.
So at least the shoulders do close and stay like this on their own.
I have to close it with the bottom holes because there is no corset lacing from the middle.
So I'll try to figure this one out.
I think one unraveled already.
So it was a bit weird.
every time I try to tighten it the latex itself stretched because it is just one
layer of latex here overall and it is not a thick latex sheet rather like the
average 0.4 mm 0.35 mm which is way too thin for corset because you don't
have any thick material you can like work against and lace it really tight so
this is like the most critical error here to just use a single sheet of latex
adding up to that the pattern is just not really developed out there compared
to the HW design one is just like a square and no hourglass shape in itself
already then we have only really really thin plastic boning so I can punch in the boning here
I shouldn't be able to do this with a corset hello in the back with the lacing you need to
have boning here as well so the lacing doesn't scrunch up or the whole thing doesn't scrunch up
no boning in the back also a critical error overall we have no figure shaping effect and
no classic corset restriction. I mean I can pull this away from me. What I can also try is how
easily I can open a seam and yeah I can just basically rip this off. It is not unusual that
you can open latex seams again if you know what you're doing and if you do it carefully.
Nevertheless it shouldn't be that easy and there was also a note which I have to read out to you
because it's hilarious. Do not use water to wash clothes for two weeks. If you want to use it
urgently please dry it because we are in order to deliver the goods in time. The glue is not
completely solidified and if there are defects in it it is inevitable. The glue is not completely
desolified is bullshit. The moment you put pressure on the garment if you make it and put the glue
on each side press it together and then really put pressure on that's the moment when the glue
solidifies to use their words. It does not take time to dry you don't have to store it in a special
place for the glue to dry it's just it doesn't work that way. If you're more interested about
have a look at the video where I made a latex bodysuit myself and you can see what I mean.
This side. What makes me kind of sad is that they put a lot of effort in this corset anyway
because you can tell there are a lot of rivets they had to do, there are a lot of buckles,
they put fabric inside here so it doesn't stretch but it's not only about the effort you put into
something it's also about craftsmanship and knowledge and from what I see here
these guys didn't know what they're doing it just feels like they saw a
picture of the original and said oh it looks like that we can also do it
without thinking further on the pattern on how it should be built from the basic
structure from the panels all that stuff which Bonin T used so it's really a shame
that they they just didn't think apparently can you wear it yes you can
is it a corset not really if you think about how corset should be and look and
feel would I buy it again for 65 bucks no would I buy it for 20 bucks no I
wouldn't buy it at all because it is just not a corset and you can save up
the money for something genuine for something that's worth the money and I'm sorry to say this
but that's a general problem with latex from China I would rather stick with the European or US
brands who have good reputation even if you have to pay more and even if you have to wait longer
but it's definitely worth the price I hope you had fun watching this video and I hope I could
enlighten you a bit about the differences in latex garments and latex
pricing. I definitely had fun this was just hilarious. I'm going to have a lot
of fun wearing my HW design corset in the future so leave a comment if you had
similar experiences with latex from China or with like cheap substitutes
from China Silos on ebay and leave a thumbs up! See you in the next video! Bye!